<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Open Internals Podcast</title>
    <link>https://openinternals.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Open Internals Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 15:19:43 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://openinternals.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>github.com/zulip/zulip</title>
      <link>https://openinternals.github.io/posts/zulip-zulip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 15:19:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openinternals.github.io/posts/zulip-zulip/</guid>
      <description>Zulip is a open source group chat application powered by a Python backend. In this podcast, I talk to Steve Howell, who is one of the longest serving core team members at Zulip.
We start with the history of Zulip and move on to talk about the architecture details including the lifecycle of a message, the major components powering Zulip, the database schema to store the messages etc.

Download</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>github.com/mholt/caddy</title>
      <link>https://openinternals.github.io/posts/mholt-caddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 15:19:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openinternals.github.io/posts/mholt-caddy/</guid>
      <description>Caddy is a cool web server written in Golang. Go standard library already has a production ready server, used to serve the chromium downloads etc, according to Andrew Gerrand. What caddy does is piggyback on that barebones implementation and add a lot of goodies to it. This includes automatic HTTPS and HTTP/2 support, QUIC support etc.
The entire project is implemented as a pluggable architecture, so much so that the &amp;ldquo;http&amp;rdquo; type of server is a plugin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Open Internals</title>
      <link>https://openinternals.github.io/posts/welcome-to-open-internals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 15:19:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openinternals.github.io/posts/welcome-to-open-internals/</guid>
      <description>There are various technical podcasts out there. Some of my favorites are the SE Radio podcast.
But none of them go as deeply into the guts of the open source packages as I would prefer. So, this I decided to roll my own podcast which is just about the technical details of open source packages.
Hope it is useful!
package main import &amp;#34;fmt&amp;#34; func main() { fmt.Println(&amp;#34;Let&amp;#39;s Roll!&amp;#34;) }</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>